Preliminary Guide to the Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc. records, 1952-2000 MS2083
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Weekend headliners, 1987-1999; Series 15; 21 Linear Feet 14 cartons
  - 1987 - 1989, audiocassettes (Carton 6)
  - 1999, miscellaneous dates, audiocassettes (Carton 7)
  - 1997 April - 1998 July, audiocassettes (Carton 8)
  - 1998 September - 1999 June, audiocassettes (Carton 9)
  - 1997 December - 1998 September, audiocassettes (Carton 10)
  - 1997 February - December, audiocassettes (Carton 11)
  - 1996 March - 1997 February, audiocassettes (Carton 12)
  - 1989 May; 1990 January 4 - 1990 October 20, audiocassettes (Carton 13, Flat box 1)
  - 1990 October 20 - 1991 August 23, audiocassettes (Carton 13, Flat box 2)
  - 1991 August 30 - 1992 March 27, audiocassettes (Carton 13, Flat box 3)
  - 1992 April 3 - 1992 December 31, audiocassettes (Carton 14, Flat box 1)
  - 1993 January 1 - December 10, audiocassettes (Carton 14, Flat box 2)
  - 1993 December 17 - 1994 December 30, audiocassettes (Carton 14, Flat box 3)
- The world this morning, 1978-1982; Series 16; 48 Linear Feet 32 cartons
  - 1978 (Carton 1)
  - 1978 February - May (Carton 2)
  - 1978 January - February (Carton 3)
  - 1977 November - 1978 January (Carton 4)
  - 1977 September - November (Carton 5)
  - 1979 January - February (Carton 6)
  - 1978 November - 1979 January (Carton 7)
  - 1978 September - November (Carton 8)
  - 1978 August - September (Carton 9)
  - 1978 June - July (Carton 10)
  - 1979 October - November (Carton 11)
  - 1979 August - October (Carton 12)
  - 1979 June - August (Carton 13)
  - 1979 April - June (Carton 14)
  - 1979 March - April (Carton 15)
  - 1980 June - August (Carton 16)
  - 1980 May - June (Carton 17)
  - 1980 March - April (Carton 18)
  - 1980 January - March (Carton 19)
  - 1979 November - 1980 January (Carton 20)
  - 1981 March - April (Carton 21)
  - 1981 January - March (Carton 22)
  - 1980 November - 1981 January (Carton 23)
  - 1980 October - November (Carton 24)
  - 1980 August - October (Carton 25)
  - 1981 November - 1981 November (Carton 26)
  - 1981 October - November (Carton 27)
  - 1981 August - October (Carton 28)
  - 1981 June - August (Carton 29)
  - 1981 June - August (Carton 30)
  - 1982 March - 1986 May (Carton 31)
  - 1982 January - March (Carton 32)
- The World today, 1958-1982; Series 17; 173 cartons
  - 1958 June 12 - 1958 September 19 (Carton 1)
  - 1958 September 22 - November 6 (Carton 2)
  - 1958 November 7 - December 29 (Carton 3)
  - 1958 December 30 - 1959 February 10 (Carton 4)
  - 1959 February 11 - March 30 (Carton 5)
  - 1959 March 31 - May 18 (Carton 6)
  - 1959 May 19 - July 8 (Carton 7)
  - 1959 July 9 - August 29 (Carton 8)
  - 1959 August 27 - October 12 (Carton 9)
  - 1959 October 14 - December 1 (Carton 10)
  - 1959 December 2 - 1960 January 14 (Carton 11)
  - 1960 January 15 - March 2 (Carton 12)
  - 1960 March 3 - April 18 (Carton 13)
  - 1960 April - June (Carton 14)
  - 1960 June - July (Carton 15)
  - 1960 July - September (Carton 16)
  - 1960 September - November (Carton 17)
  - 1960 November - December (Carton 18)
  - 1960 December - 1961 February (Carton 19)
  - 1961 February - April (Carton 20)
  - 1961 April - May (Carton 21)
  - 1961 May - July (Carton 22)
  - 1961 July - September (Carton 23)
  - 1961 September - November (Carton 24)
  - 1961 November - December (Carton 25)
  - 1961 December - 1962 February (Carton 26)
  - 1962 February - April (Carton 27)
  - 1962 April - May (Carton 28)
  - 1962 June - July (Carton 29)
  - 1962 July - September (Carton 30)
  - 1962 September - October (Carton 31)
  - 1962 October - December (Carton 32)
  - 1962 December - 1963 February (Carton 33)
  - 1963 February - March (Carton 34)
  - 1963 April - May (Carton 35)
  - 1963 May - June (Carton 36)
  - 1963 June - August (Carton 37)
  - 1963 August - September (Carton 38)
  - 1963 September - November (Carton 39)
  - 1963 November - December (Carton 40)
  - 1963 December - 1964 February (Carton 41)
  - 1964 February - March (Carton 42)
  - 1964 March - April (Carton 43)
  - 1964 April - June (Carton 44)
  - 1964 June - August (Carton 45)
  - 1964 August - September (Carton 46)
  - 1964 September - October (Carton 47)
  - 1964 October - December (Carton 48)
  - 1964 December - 1965 January (Carton 49)
  - 1965 January - March (Carton 50)
  - 1965 March - April (Carton 51)
  - 1965 May - June (Carton 52)
  - 1965 June - July (Carton 53)
  - 1965 July - August (Carton 54)
  - 1965 September - October (Carton 55)
  - 1965 October - November (Carton 56)
  - 1965 December - 1966 January (Carton 57)
  - 1966 January - March (Carton 58)
  - 1966 March - April (Carton 59)
  - 1966 April - May (Carton 60)
  - 1966 May 30 - July 10 (Carton 61)
  - 1966 July 11 - August 19 (Carton 62)
  - 1966 August 21 - October 4 (Carton 63)
  - 1966 October 5 - November 15 (Carton 64)
  - 1966 November 16 - December 28 (Carton 65)
  - 1966 December 29 - 1967 February 9 (Carton 66)
  - 1967 February 10 - March 25 (Carton 67)
  - 1967 March 26 - May 9 (Carton 68)
  - 1967 May 10 - June 22 (Carton 69)
  - 1967 June 23 - August 7 (Carton 70)
  - 1967 August 8 - September 21 (Carton 71)
  - 1967 September 23 - November 3 (Carton 72)
  - 1967 November 4 - December 16 (Carton 73)
  - 1967 December 15 - 1968 January 29 (Carton 74)
  - 1968 January 30 - March 16 (Carton 75)
  - 1968 March 18 - April 30 (Carton 76)
  - 1968 May 16 - June 11 (Carton 77)
  - 1968 June 12 - July 27 (Carton 78)
  - 1968 July 30 - September 9 (Carton 79)
  - 1968 September 11 - October 22 (Carton 80)
  - 1968 October 24 - December 7 (Carton 81)
  - 1968 December 9 - 1967 January 31 (Carton 82)
  - 1969 February 1 - March 16 (Carton 83)
  - 1969 March 17 - May 1 (Carton 84)
  - 1969 May 2 - June 23 (Carton 85)
  - 1969 June 24 - August 13 (Carton 86)
  - 1969 August 14 - October 5 (Carton 87)
  - 1969 October 6 - November 27 (Carton 88)
  - 1969 November 28 - 1970 January 20 (Carton 89)
  - 1970 January 21 - March 16 (Carton 90)
  - 1970 March 17 - May 7 (Carton 91)
  - 1970 May 8 - June 26 (Carton 92)
  - 1970 June 29 - August 17 (Carton 93)
  - 1970 August 18 - October 7 (Carton 94)
  - 1970 October 8 - November 27 (Carton 95)
  - 1970 November 30 - 1971 January 18 (Carton 96)
  - 1971 January 19 - March 3 (Carton 97)
  - 1971 March 4 - April 30 (Carton 98)
  - 1971 May 3 - June 14 (Carton 99)
  - 1976 January 1 - February 19 (Carton 100)
  - 1976 February 20 - April 15 (Carton 101)
  - 1976 April 10 - June 8 (Carton 102)
  - 1976 June 9 - July 29 (Carton 103)
  - 1976 July 30 - September 21 (Carton 104)
  - 1977 April 13 - May 30 (Carton 105)
  - 1974 February 18 - April 12 (Carton 106)
  - 1976 December 29 - 1977 February 17 (Carton 107)
  - 1976 November 10 - December 25 (Carton 108)
  - 1976 September 22 - November 9 (Carton 109)
  - 1971 August 20 - November 13 (Carton 110)
  - 1971 June 30 - August 19 (Carton 111)
  - 1971 April 6 - June 29 (Carton 112)
  - 1977 July 29 - September 5 (Carton 113)
  - 1977 May 31 - July 28 (Carton 114)
  - 1972 December 19 - 1974 April 26 (Carton 115)
  - 1972 May 12 - December 19 (Carton 116)
  - 1972 January 6 - May 23 (Carton 117)
  - 1971 December 6 - 1972 January (Carton 118)
  - 1971 October 14 - December 3 (Carton 119)
  - 1974 November 20 - 1975 January 10 (Carton 120)
  - 1974 October 2 - November 19 (Carton 121)
  - 1974 August 9 - October 1 (Carton 122)
  - 1974 June 19 - August 8 (Carton 123)
  - 1974 April 29 - June 18 (Carton 124)
  - 1975 August 12 - October 2 (Carton 125)
  - 1975 June 24 - October 2 (Carton 126)
  - 1975 June 23 - 24 (Carton 127)
  - 1975 June 23 (Carton 128)
  - 1975 January 13 - March 5 (Carton 129)
  - 1978 February 7 - March 24 (Carton 130)
  - 1978 February 6 - December 15 (Carton 131)
  - 1973 December 14 - 1974 October 25 (Carton 132)
  - 1974 October 25 - November 18 (Carton 133)
  - 1975 October 3 - November 17 (Carton 134)
  - 1978 October 23 - December 11 (Carton 135)
  - 1978 August 31 - October 20 (Carton 136)
  - 1978 July 11 - August 30 (Carton 137)
  - 1978 May 18 - July 10 (Carton 138)
  - 1978 March 28 - May 17 (Carton 139)
  - 1979 July 4 - August 23 (Carton 140)
  - 1979 May 14 - June 11 (Carton 141)
  - 1979 February 26 - May 11 (Carton 142)
  - 1979 February 1 - March 23 (Carton 143)
  - 1978 December 12 - 1979 January 31 (Carton 144)
  - 1980 March 14 - May 2 (Carton 145)
  - 1979 December 5 - 1980 December 3 (Carton 147)
  - 1979 October 15 - December 4 (Carton 148)
  - 1979 October 24 - November 12 (Carton 149)
  - 1980 November 26 - 1981 January 4 (Carton 150)
  - 1980 October 26 - November 25 (Carton 151)
  - 1980 August 15 - October 3 (Carton 152)
  - 1980 June 24 - August 15 (Carton 153)
  - 1980 May 5 - June 23 (Carton 154)
  - 1981 January 15 - March 5 (Carton 155)
  - 1981 March 6 - April 27 (Carton 156)
  - 1981 April 28 - June 16 (Carton 157)
  - 1981 June 27 - August 10 (Carton 158)
  - 1981 August 11 - September 28 (Carton 159)
  - 1981 September 29 - November 17 (Carton 160)
  - 1982 January 8 - February 25 (Carton 161)
  - 1981 November 18 - 1982 January 9 (Carton 162)
  - 1982 March 19 - August 26 (Carton 163)
  - 1983 July - October (Carton 164)
  - 1983 March - June (Carton 165)
  - 1982 November - 1983 February (Carton 166)
  - 1982 April - October (Carton 167)
  - 1982 March; 1985 March (Carton 168)
  - 1982 February - March (Carton 169)
  - 1984 November - 1985 January (Carton 170)
  - 1984 July - October (Carton 171)
  - 1984 March - June (Carton 172)
  - 1983 November - 1984 February (Carton 173)
- Subject files, Series 18
  - Iranian Hostages return, 1981
    - Hostages return, audiotapes (Carton 1)
    - Hostages return, audiotapes (Carton 2)
  - Obituaries, undated
    Prepared for famous politicians, celebrities, etc. to be used in the event of their deaths.
    Audio tapes, some 8-track.
    - A - Beale (Carton 1)
    - Berman - Busey (Carton 2)
    - Downs - Frost (Carton 3)
    - Gar - Ham (Carton 4)
    - Caesar - Cong (Carton 5)
    - Conwers - Downey (Carton 6)
    - Hawks - Ives (Carton 7)
    - J - King (Carton 8)
    - Kissinger - Lyndew (Carton 9)
    - M - Newhart (Carton 10)
    - Newman - Peck (Carton 11)
    - Pickew - Regaw (Carton 12)
    - Rehnquist - Salinger (Carton 13)
    - Schlafley - Slater (Carton 14)
    - Slick - Sworthout (Carton 15)
    - Taylor - Tutu (Carton 16)
    - V - Wallach (Carton 17)
    - Wallop - Winters (Carton 18)
    - Wolff - Z (Carton 19)
  - O.J. Simpson trial, 1994-1998; Series 17 Subseries 3
    Box 1 contains Tom Brokaw reports, 1997-1998.
    - Brokaw reports, 1997 - 1998; audiotapes (Carton 1)
    - 1994 - 1995, audiotapes (Carton 2)
    - 1994 - 1995, audiotapes (Carton 3)
    - 1994 - 1995, audiotapes (Carton 4)
    - 1994 - 1995, audiotapes (Carton 5)
  - Persian Gulf war, 1991
    - 1991 (Carton 1)
    - 1991 (Carton 2)
  - Political conventions, 1980
    - Democratic convention, 1980 (Carton 1)
    - Republican convention, 1980 (Carton 2)
  - Political/Historical events, 1960-1985; 37.5 Linear Feet 25 cartons
    - Nix 46 - 85 (Carton 1)
    - Car 46 - GRF 1 (Carton 2)
    - GRF 4 - GRF 59 (Carton 3)
    - 1980 YNR CAR 45 (Carton 4)
    - GRF 66 - JFK 22 (Carton 5)
    - JFK 23 - 58 (Carton 6)
    - JFK 182 - Nix 45 (Carton 7)
    - Pop 36 - yed 32 (Carton 8)
    - Ada 1 - Pop 35 (Carton 9)
    - Ada 1 - Pop 35 (Carton 9)
    - Ada 1 - Pop 35 (Carton 9)
    - Yea 1 - 1980 YW Rev (Carton 10)
    - Pol 161 - Pol 240 (Carton 11)
    - Pol 293 - Mon 25 (Carton 12)
    - His 96 - JFK 139 (Carton 13)
    - JFK 59 - 95 (Carton 14)
    - JFK 140 - 186 (Carton 15)
    - SkyLabCK - Ap125 (Carton 16)
    - Nix 27 - Pol 142 (Carton 17)
    - Nix 84 - Nix 120 (Carton 18)
    - RFX 17 - STA 1 (Carton 19)
    - NIX 121 - RFK 16 (Carton 20)
    - JFK 2 - NIX 124 (Carton 21)
    - Poll 53 - Elec 76 (Carton 22)
    - Car 74 - GRF 15 (Carton 23)
    - GRF 17 - JFK 1 (Carton 24)
    - BRA 1 - CAR 73 (Carton 25)
  - President Bill Clinton, 1993-1998
    - 1998, audiotapes (Carton 1)
    - 1993 - 1996, audiotapes (Carton 2)
    - 1996 - 1998, audiotapes (Carton 3)
    - 1995, audiotapes (Carton 4)
    - 1997, audiotapes (Carton 5)
    - 1995 - 1996, audiotapes (Carton 6)
    - 1992 (Carton 1)
  - President George Bush, 1989-1992
    Box 1 contains tapes that belong to the President Clinton subseries.
    - Bush, 1992 (Carton 1)
      Box 1 also contains President Clinton tapes.
    - 1991-1992 (Carton 2)
    - 1989-1990 (Carton 3)
  - President Ronald Reagan, 1981-1986
    - 1982 - 1983 (Carton 1)
    - undated (Carton 2)
    - 1982 - 1984 (Carton 3)
    - 1985 - 1986 (Carton 4)
    - 1983 - 1985 (Carton 5)
    - 1981 November - 1982 February (Carton 6)
    - 1982 (Carton 7)
    - 1981 May - October (Carton 8)
    - 1982 February - 1985 May (Carton 9)
    - 1981 May - October (Carton 10)
    - 1982 February - 1985 May (Carton 11)
    - 1982 (Carton 12)
  - President Reagan cabinet confirmation hearings, 1981
    - 1981 January (Carton 1)
    - 1981 January (Carton 2)
    - 1981 January (Carton 3)
    - 1981 January (Carton 4)
  - Special events, 1963-1998
    - 1995 - 1997 (Carton 1)
    - 1997 - 1998 (Carton 2)
    - 1994 - 1995 (Carton 3)
    - 1994 - 1995 (Carton 3)
    - 1992 - 1994 (Carton 4)
    - 1979 August - 1989 January (Carton 5)
    - Mill., undated (Carton 6)
    - 1988 (Carton 7)
    - 1992 (Carton 8)
    - 1998 (Carton 9)
    - 1989 January - 1999 April (Carton 10)
    - 1968 - 1980 (Carton 11)
    - 1981 (Carton 12)
    - 1981 - 1982 (Carton 13)
    - 1987 (Carton 14)
    - 1980 - 1981 (Carton 15)
    - 1982 - 1986 (Carton 16)
    - 1968, 1988 - 1989 (Carton 17)
    - 1986 - 1987 (Carton 18)
    - 1987 - 1988 (Carton 19)
    - 1963 - 1968 (Carton 20)
    - 1990 - 1991 (Carton 21)
    - 1989 - 1990 (Carton 22)
    - 1988 (Carton 23)
    - 1989 (Carton 24)
    - undated (Carton 25)
    - 1991 (Carton 26)
    - 1992 (Carton 27)
    - 1991 - 1992 (Carton 28)
    - 1988 (Carton 29)
    - 1992 - 1994 (Carton 30)
    - 1991 March 22 - 1991 August 9 (Carton 31)
    - 1994 September - 1995 March (Carton 32)
    - 1991 August 22 - 1992 November 16 (Carton 33)
    - 1990 June 2 - 1991 March 22 (Carton 34)
    - 1989 February 29 - 1990 May 10 (Carton 35)
    - 1987 August 26 - 1989 January 4 (Carton 36)
    - 1986 April 1 - 1987 August 12 (Carton 37)
    - 1985 February 6 - 1986 March 6 (Carton 38)
    - 1984 July 26 - 1985 February 5 (Carton 39)
    - 1985 October 6 - 1989 July 25 (Carton 40)
    - 1981 - 1985 October 6 (Carton 41)
    - 1980 - 1981 (Carton 42)
    - 1972 - 1980 (Carton 43)
    - 19?7 - 1972 (Carton 44)
    - Sx Eocas Iran - Contras, 1991 - 1995 (Carton 45)
    - Campaigns, assorted, 1989 - 1991 (Carton 46)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Carton 47)
    - Iran Contra, undated (Carton 48)
    - Old radio shows, undated (Carton 49)
    - Democratic / Republican conventions, undated (Carton 50)
    - Special events, undated (Carton 51)
    - 1995 March - 1997 July (Carton 52)
  - Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas hearings, 1991
    - 1991 (Carton 1)
    - 1991 (Carton 2)
  - Jackie Robinson, Women in the military, and Miscellaneous tapes, [ca. 1970-1981]
    Audio tapes and paper records. Includes NBC Today show, NBC History ACK cuts, NBC Super Rocky specials, 1974 (featuring The Who, Moody Blues, Sha Na Na, Bobby Womak, Deep Purple, Al Green, Stylistics, Eddie Kendricks, Jerry Garcia, Blue Magic), Second Sunday (1972-1978). Paper records include Montier/Galaxie interview transcripts, Lebanon hostage briefing book, Liberty Weekend briefing book (1977-1981).
    - Miscellaneous women in the military, 1991 (Carton 1)
    - NBC history ACK cuts, undated (Carton 2)
    - Paper records, undated (Carton 3)
    - NBC Today Bday, undated (Carton 4)
    - NBC Super Rock, 1974 (Carton 5)
    - Wom. pg, 1979 (Carton 5)
    - NBC music, 1980 (Carton 6)
    - Second sunday, 1972 - 1978 (Carton 7)
    - Jackie Robinson, undated (Carton 8)
- Golden recordings, Series 19
  - Golden reels/Golden cassettes finding aids ("Golden Sheets"), 1980-1998; Series 19 Subseries 1
    Printed abstracts of shows in the "Golden reels/Golden cassettes" series.
    - 1980 December - 1981 March (Carton 1)
    - 1980 December - 1981 March (Carton 2)
    - 1981 April - July (Carton 3)
    - 1981 April - July (Carton 4)
    - 1981 August - November (Carton 5)
    - 1981 August - November (Carton 6)
    - 1981 December - 1982 March (Carton 7)
    - 1981 December - 1982 March (Carton 8)
    - 1982 April - June (Carton 9)
    - 1982 April - June (Carton 10)
    - 1982 July - August (Carton 11)
    - 1982 July - August (Carton 12)
    - 1982 October (Carton 13)
    - 1982 October (Carton 14)
    - 1982 November - December (Carton 15)
    - 1982 November - December (Carton 16)
    - 1983 January - February (Carton 17)
    - 1983 January - February (Carton 18)
    - 1983 March - April (Carton 19)
    - 1983 March - April (Carton 20)
    - 1983 May - June (Carton 21)
    - 1983 May - June (Carton 22)
    - 1983 July - August (Carton 23)
    - 1983 July - August (Carton 24)
    - 1983 September - October (Carton 25)
    - 1983 September - October (Carton 26)
    - 1983 November - December (Carton 27)
    - 1983 November - December (Carton 28)
    - 1984 January - February (Carton 29)
    - 1984 January - February (Carton 30)
    - 1984 March - April (Carton 31)
    - 1984 March - April (Carton 32)
    - 1984 May - June (Carton 33)
    - 1984 May - June (Carton 34)
    - 1984 May - June (Carton 34)
    - 1984 July - August (Carton 35)
    - 1984 July - August (Carton 36)
    - 1984 September - October (Carton 37)
    - 1984 September - October (Carton 38)
    - 1984 November - December (Carton 39)
    - 1984 November - December (Carton 40)
    - 1985 January - February (Carton 41)
    - 1985 January - February (Carton 42)
    - 1985 March - April (Carton 43)
    - 1985 March - April (Carton 44)
    - 1985 April - May (Carton 45)
    - 1985 April - May (Carton 46)
    - 1985 July (Carton 47)
    - 1985 August (Carton 48)
    - 1985 September - October (Carton 49)
    - 1985 September - October (Carton 50)
    - 1985 November (Carton 51)
    - 1985 December (Carton 52)
    - 1985 January - February (Carton 53)
    - 1985 March (Carton 54)
    - 1986 (Carton 55)
    - 1987 (Carton 56)
    - 1988 January - July (Carton 57)
    - 1988 January - July (Carton 58)
    - 1988 August - October (Carton 59)
    - 1988 August - October (Carton 60)
    - 1988 December - 1989 February (Carton 61)
    - 1988 December - 1989 February (Carton 62)
    - 1989 March - June (Carton 63)
    - 1989 March - June (Carton 64)
    - 1989 April - September (Carton 65)
    - 1989 April - September (Carton 66)
    - 1989 October - December (Carton 67)
    - 1990 January - July (Carton 68)
    - 1990 January - July (Carton 69)
    - 1990 August - December (Carton 70)
    - 1990 August - December (Carton 71)
    - 1991 January - August (Carton 72)
    - 1991 January - August (Carton 73)
    - 1991 January - August (Carton 74)
    - 1991 September - November (Carton 75)
    - 1980 May - November (Carton 76)
    - 1980 May - November (Carton 77)
  - Golden reels/Golden cassettes, 1980-1998; Series 19 Subseries 2; 102 Linear Feet 68 cartons
    - 1986 January - September, audiotape reels (Carton 1)
    - 1986 October - 1987 June, audiotape reels (Carton 2)
    - 1987 June - 1988 February, audiotape reels (Carton 3)
    - 1988 February - June, audiotape reels (Carton 4)
    - 1988 July - August, audiotape reels (Carton 5)
    - 1988 July - August, audiotape reels (Carton 5)
    - 1988 September - October, audiotape reels (Carton 6)
    - 1988 October - 1989 January, audiotape reels (Carton 7)
    - 1989 January - March, audiotape reels (Carton 8)
    - 1989 January - March, audiotape reels (Carton 8)
    - 1989 April - May, audiotape reels (Carton 9)
    - 1989 June - July, audiotape reels (Carton 10)
    - 1989 August - October, audiotape reels (Carton 11)
    - 1989 October - December, audiotape reels (Carton 12)
    - 1989 December - 1990 February, audiotape reels (Carton 13)
    - 1990 February - May, audiotape reels (Carton 14)
    - 1990 May - September, audiotape reels (Carton 15)
    - 1990 September - December, audiotape reels (Carton 16)
    - 1991 January - March, audiotape reels (Carton 17)
    - 1991 March - June, audiotape reels (Carton 18)
    - 1991 June - September, audiotape reels (Carton 19)
    - 1991 September - December, audiotape reels (Carton 20)
    - 1991 December - 1992 March, audiotape reels (Carton 21)
    - 1992 March - June, audiotape reels (Carton 22)
    - 1992 June - August, audiotape reels (Carton 23)
    - 1992 August - November, audiotape reels (Carton 24)
    - 1992 November - 1993 February, audiotape reels (Carton 25)
    - 1993 February - May, audiotape reels (Carton 26)
    - 1993 May - October, audiotape reels (Carton 27)
    - 1994 August - November, audiotape reels (Carton 28)
    - 1994 November - 1995 March, audiotape reels (Carton 29)
    - 1993 October - 1994 February, audiotape reels (Carton 30)
    - 1994 February - July, audiotape reels (Carton 31)
    - 1995 March - June, audiotape reels (Carton 32)
    - 1995 June - September, audiotape reels (Carton 33)
    - 1995 September - December, audiotape reels (Carton 34)
    - 1995 December - 1996 March, audiotape reels (Carton 35)
    - 1996 March - June, audiotape reels (Carton 36)
    - 1996 June - August, audiotape reels (Carton 37)
    - 1996 August - October, audiotape reels (Carton 38)
    - 1996 October - 1997 January, audiotape reels (Carton 39)
    - 1997 January - March, audiotape reels (Carton 40)
    - 1997 May - July, audiotape reels (Carton 41)
    - 1997 July - October, audiotape reels (Carton 42)
    - 1997 October - 1998 January, audiotape reels (Carton 43)
    - 1998 January - May, audiotape reels (Carton 44)
    - 1998 May - August, audiotape reels (Carton 45)
    - 1980 May - August, audiocassettes (Carton 46)
    - 1980 September - December, audiocassettes (Carton 47)
    - 1981 January - May, audiocassettes (Carton 48)
    - 1981 June - September, audiocassettes (Carton 49)
    - 1981 October - 1982 January, audiocassettes (Carton 50)
    - 1982 February - April, audiocassettes (Carton 51)
    - 1982 May - August, audiocassettes (Carton 52)
    - 1982 October - December, audiocassettes (Carton 53)
    - 1983 January - April, audiocassettes (Carton 54)
    - 1983 May - August, audiocassettes (Carton 55)
    - 1983 September - December, audiocassettes (Carton 56)
    - 1984 January - March, audiocassettes (Carton 57)
    - 1984 May - September, audiocassettes (Carton 58)
    - 1984 September - December, audiocassettes (Carton 59)
    - 1985 January - March, audiocassettes (Carton 60)
    - 1985 May - September, audiocassettes (Carton 61)
    - 1985 September - December, audiocassettes (Carton 62)
    - 1986 January - 1987, audiocassettes (Carton 63)
    - 1988 - 1989, audiocassettes (Carton 64)
    - 1989 - 1991, audiocassettes (Carton 65)
    - 1992 - 1994, audiocassettes (Carton 66)
    - 1995 - 1997, audiocassettes (Carton 67)
    - 1997 - 1998, audiocassettes (Carton 68)
- RKO files, Series 20; 30 Linear Feet
  - RKO cut sheets, 1980-1989; 7.5 Linear Feet 5 cartons
    Printed sheets of "cuts" from RKO morgue.
    - 1980 - 1989 (Carton 1)
    - 1980 - 1989 (Carton 2)
    - 1980 - 1989 (Carton 3)
    - 1980 - 1989 (Carton 4)
    - 1988 - 1989 (Carton 5)
  - RKO morgue, 1980-1989; 21 Linear Feet 14 cartons
    - 1983 - 1984 (Carton 1)
    - 1988 (Carton 2)
    - 1982 - 1983 (Carton 3)
    - 1989 (Carton 4)
    - 1985 - 1987 (Carton 5)
    - 1980, 1982, 1989 (Carton 6)
    - 1987 - 1988 (Carton 7)
    - 1984 - 1985 (Carton 8)
    - 1988 (Carton 9)
    - 1980 - 1981 (Carton 10)
    - 1988 - 1989 (Carton 11)
    - 1982, 1983, 1985, 1986 (Carton 12)
    - 1988 - 1989 (Carton 14)